Felipe Costa Godoi Uberaba – MG – Brazil

feeh.08.2001@gmail.com

Single

Neighborhood: Santa Maria - Uberaba

12/01/2001

Phone: +55 34 997651567

Linkedin: https://www.linkedin.com/in/felipe-godoi

Website: <a href="https://godoi.dev">https://godoi.dev</a>

# **OBJECTIVE: Back-end Developer**

#### **Education**

Bachelor's Degree in Computer Engineering – Instituto Federal do Triângulo Mineiro (IFTM). Postgraduate Lato Sensu, Specialization in Blockchain Development – UniFECAF Postgraduate Lato Sensu, Specialization in Distributed Systems Architecture – PUC Minas

## **QUALIFICATION SUMMARY**

I have been developing since I was 14 but began my professional career at 18. I have over 4 years of experience in software development. During this time, I have primarily worked as a full-stack developer with a focus on back-end, engaging in all necessary areas: front-end, back-end, infrastructure, databases, etc. I have always been driven by a strong curiosity to learn different technologies. My main experience includes Node and Angular, but I have also worked with Python, C#, Rust, Java, and most recently, I have been studying Web3 with Solidity. I hold a Bachelor's degree in Computer Engineering and am currently pursuing postgraduate specializations in Distributed Software Architecture and Blockchain Development.

## PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

# TALENT ACADEMY - May 2022 - Present

#### **Backend Developer (Node.is)**

Responsibilities include enhancement and maintenance of a web platform used for Digital HR solutions. I address bug fixes, discuss architectures and technologies, and develop new tools. Technologies used: Node.js, Angular, MySQL, GCP.

## DPROWARE, YOUR SOFTWARE FACTORY – February 2021 – April 2022

#### **Backend Developer (Node.js)**

Provided consultancy for companies as a software factory. Worked with various clients to develop integrations between their logistic systems and point of sale, in addition to providing general technological solutions. Technologies used: Node.js, Angular, .NET Framework, React, Ionic, SQL Server, Windows Server.

# MULLTIPLA MANAGEMENT PLATFORM FOR DISTRIBUTORS AND INDUSTRIES— January 2020 – February 2021

## **Backend Developer Intern (Node.js)**

Developed an app for logistics and WMS. Led the development of the app architecture and the APIs that processed and managed data received by logistic systems. Technologies used: Node.js, SQL Server, Ionic, Angular, Windows Server.

## PROFESSIONAL DEVELOPMENT

SOLID with Java: Object-Oriented Programming Principles – Alura

GPT and Python: Creating Tools with the API – Alura

Exploring Vue3 Framework – Alura

NestJS from Scratch with TypeORM, Mongoose, Prisma, and Swagger – Udemy

The Complete Python Course | Learn Python by Doing in 2024 – Udemy

The Development Fundamentals – 101 Blockchains

Solidity Fundamentals – 101 Blockchains

Bitcoin Programming - UniFECAF